Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: Research Files
  - Subseries 4: Hanigan Case Research Files
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -National Coalition on the Hanigan Case: Miscellaneous Materials (Pt.2), 1979-1981, No date (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Raw Notes (Pt.1), No Date (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Raw Notes (Pt.2), No date (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Tom Miller writings, 1981, No date (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 5: La Bamba Research Files
    - Research Files -La Bamba -African Influences, 1987-1990, No date (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Artists, 1982-1988, No date (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Best of Album, 1987-1990, No date (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Bob Keane, 1951-1985, No date (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Correspondence, 1987-1993, No date (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Documentary with North South Production, 1988-1989, No date (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -General, 1986-2000, No date (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -History of song, 1976-1987, No date (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -La Bamba Essays, Multiple drafts, No date (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -La Bamba Essay Spanish Translation, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -La Bamba Movie, 1987, No date (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -La Bamba Movie Screenplay, May 28, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Magazine Article Information, 1986-1987, No date (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Mexico, 1940-1987, No date (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Miscellaneous Materials, 1987-1999, No date (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Notes, No date (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Richie Valens, 1959-1987, No date (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -La Bamba -Tom Miller La Bamba Song, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 6: Tom Miller Grand Jury Case Research Files
    - Research Files -Tom Miller Grand Jury Case -Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Tom Miller Grand Jury Case -Affidavits, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Tom Miller Grand Jury Case -Legal Documents, 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Tom Miller Grand Jury Case -Miscellaneous Materials (Includes Photographs), No date (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Tom Miller Grand Jury Case -Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1976, No date (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 7: Raw Notes Research Files
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Cuba, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Cuba, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Ecuador (Pt.1), 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Ecuador (Pt.2), 1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -"Long Time Gone", 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Miscellaneous Notes (Pt.1), 1989-1997 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Miscellaneous Notes (Pt.2), No date (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Miscellaneous Notes (Pt.3), No date (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Raw Notes -Miscellaneous Notes (Pt.4), No date (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 8: Self Clips Research Files
    - Research Files -Self Clips -Correspondence, 1991-2001, No date (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Self Clips -Events and Press Releases, 1980-2002, No date (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Self Clips -Miscellaneous, 1963-2002, No date (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Self Clips -Newspaper Articles (Pt.1), 1970-1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Self Clips -Newspaper Articles (Pt.2), 1997-2002, No date (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -Self Clips -Programs and Conferences, 1963-2001, No date (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Series III: Personal Files
  - Personal Files -Certificates, 1973-1994 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Personal Files -Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Personal Files -High School Materials, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Personal Files -Miscellaneous Materials, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Personal Files -Photographs, No date (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Personal Files -University of Arizona -Employment, 1979,1999 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Personal Files -University of Arizona -Latin American Area Center, 1990, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Personal Files -Teaching Materials -Essays, 1978-1999, No date (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Personal Files -Teaching Materials -General, 1974-1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Personal Files -Teaching Materials -Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Personal Files -Phone Books, No date (Box 51)
  - Personal Files -Planners, 1977-2001 (Box 52)
- Series IV: Salt of the Earth (Film)
  - Subseries 1: FBI Files
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Correspondence -Incoming, 1982-1989 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Correspondence -Outgoing, 1982-1984 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Freedom of Information Act, No date (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Salt of the -FBI Files -Juan Chacón -File Number Albuquerque 100-975 (Pt.1), 1951-1983 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Juan Chacón -File Number Albuquerque 100-975 (Pt.2), 1951-1983 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Juan Chacón -File Number AQ 100-975, 1953-1983 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Juan Chacón -File Number FBIHQ 100-385182, 1953-1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Virginia Chacón -File Number 100-385183, 1970-1990 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Virginia Chacón -File Number Albuquerque 100-969, 1951-1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Virginia Chacón -File Number AQ 100-968, 1955-1990 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Virginia Chacón -File Number FBIHQ 100-385183, 1951-1983 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Miscellaneous Documents, 1953-1954 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth Documents for the CIA, 1953-1983 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-399257 sub. A, 1953-1984 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-299257 section 1, 1953-1983 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-299257 section 2, 1953-1989 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-299257 section 3, 1954-1983 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-399257 section 4, 1959-1983 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-399257 section 1, 1953-1988 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-399257 section 2, 1953-1988 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Salt of the Earth -FBI Files -Salt of the Earth -File Number 100-399257 section 3, 1954-1988 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2: Research Files, Audio, and Photograph Files
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Correspondence -Article Related, 1981-1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Correspondence -Mining, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Blacklist, 1952-1997, No date (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Book Review, No date (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Commentary, 1953-1983, No date (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Congress 1953 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -"A Crime to Fit a Punishment", 1982, No date (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Esperanza, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Filming, 1951-1976 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Grant County, New Mexico Unemployment, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Juan Chacón, 1975-1985, No date (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Local #890, 1976-1982, No date (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Miscellaneous Materials, 1952-2002, No date (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Movie, 1952-1998 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Note Cards, No date (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Notes, 1982, No date (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Rosaura Revueltas, 1953-1996 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -"Salt: A Story About a Film", 1984-1985, No date (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Silver City, 1970-1983, No date (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Thesis, "Empire and Opposition" 1979 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Salt of the Earth -Research Files -Manuscript Articles, 1982-1984, No date (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Salt of the Earth -Audio Tapes, 1978, No date (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Salt of the Earth -Photographs, 1954-1981 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Series V: Manuscripts by other Authors
  - Manuscripts by other Authors -Baker, Christopher P. Mi Moto Fidel, No date (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Manuscripts by other Authors -Brent, William Lee Long Time Gone (Pt.1), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Manuscripts by other Authors -Brent, William Lee Long Time Gone (Pt.2), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Manuscripts by other Authors -Brent, William Lee Long Time Gone (Pt.3), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Manuscripts by other Authors -Brent, William Lee Long Time Gone (Pt.4), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Manuscripts by other Authors -Kufeld, Adam Cuba, Introduction by Tom Miller, No date (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - ACE, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - All You Can Eat, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - AMEX: The American Expatriate, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Anarchy Comics, 1978-1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - AMPO: A Report from the Japanese, No. 5, No date (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Apex Treasury of Underground Comics, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Are you Weird? Committee on Free Culture, No date (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Armadilla, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Armadillo Comics Two, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Atlanta Gazette, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Attitude Check, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Austin Sun, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Basta Ya!, 1969 (?) (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Berkeley Barb, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Bicentennial Gross-outs, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Big Fat Magazine, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Black Community News, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Black Panthers, The Adventures of Black Eldridge, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Black Power, A Collection of Statements and Interviews, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Boulder Alternative Press, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Bullshit, National Lawyers Guild, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Carolina Israelite, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Cartoon History of the Universe, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Catalogue 12, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Challenge, The Revolutionary Newspaper, No date (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Commies from Mars, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Corporate Crime Comics, No date (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Corporate Crime Comics, 1977-1979 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Counter Attack, No date (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Cover-up Lowdown, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Cultural Correspondence, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Dallas News, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Dallas Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Denuncia! (Pt.1) No. 4-78, No date (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Denuncia! (Pt.2) No. 1-132, No date (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Denuncia! (Pt.3) No.184-630, No date (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Dope Sheet, No date (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Dragon, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Dripping Springs Reunion, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Druid Free Press, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Duck Power, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Flash, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Free Palestine, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Free Ranger Intertribal News, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Free Toilet, Inauguration Washington, No date (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Door, 1971(?) (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Earth First (Pt.1), 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Earth First (Pt.2), 1985 (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Carolina Israelite, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Earth First (Pt.3), 1986 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Earth First (Pt.4), 1987-1988 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Earth First (Pt.5), 1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Earth First (Pt.6), 1990-1992, No date (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Fat Freddy's Cat, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Freak Brothers, 1980-1992 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - GI Rebellion, No date (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Glyptodon News, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Good Times, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Gotham City, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Great Psychiatric Front (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Great Speckled Bird, 1969-1972 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Griffith Observatory, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Grump, 1965-1967 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Guardian (Pt.1), 1968-1970 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Guardian (Pt.2), 1968-1970 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Handwriting on the Wall #2, No date (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Hardtimes (formerly May Day) (Pt.1), 1968-1970 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Hardtimes (formerly May Day) (Pt.2), 1968-1970 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Harper's Weekly, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Harvill to Speak, No date (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Healthy Rights News, 1967-1968 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Horse Shit, 1967-1968 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -How Harvard Rules, No date (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -How to Expose and Fight the Democratic Party in your Community, No date (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - HUP, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Iconoclast, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - I.F. Stone's Bi-weekly, 1966-1971 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Kent Prangon Fire, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Labor Defender, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Liberated Guardian, 1970-1972 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Liberation, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Lone Star Dispatch, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Loretta Lynn Fan Club, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Los Angeles Press, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Mac Bird, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Mad Funk vol.1 no.1, No date (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Manhattan Tribune, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Match, Anarchist Monthly, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Michigan Daily, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Mockingbird, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Mother Oats Comix, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Motor City Comics, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The New Adventures of Jesus, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The New Leader, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - New Times, 1971-1973 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - New Times Magazine, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The New York News Service, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Newsreel Catalog, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Not Quite Dead, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Oberlin Review, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - On the Resistance, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Osawatomie, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Other, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Outlaw, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Pac-O-Lies, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Paramilitary Right, No date (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Peace and Freedom National Organizer, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Philadelphia Free Press, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Phonographic Record Magazine, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Plain Dealer, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Playbill Hair, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Pogo and Albert, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Porkpie Magazine, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Port Huron Statement, 1962(?) (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Pousto, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Prairie Fire, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Protest, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Quicksilver Times, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Rabadash, A Thistle Publication, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Rag, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Rama Pipien, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Ramparts (Pt.1), 1968-1970 (Box 58, Folder 46)